To see or change your child’s privacy settings,
make sure you’re signed in as you.
Go to Settings . . . All settings.
Under Account . . . choose Family.
Select your child’s gamerpic.
If it isn’t there, add your child’s profile to your family
by selecting Add to family.
If you still don’t see their gamerpic, download their profile
by selecting Add new and following the steps.
If they don’t have an Xbox Live profile, you can also create one here.
After you select their gamerpic, choose Privacy & online safety.
Smart defaults based on age are already set, and you can adjust them.
Select View details & customize.
Read about and set each option the way you prefer.
Your child won’t be able to change these settings themselves.
When you’re done, go back a few screens and
select Access to content, which determines the rating levels
of games, TV, movies, and apps your child can use.
Web filtering limits Internet access while browsing on the Xbox One.
And Contact preferences lets you choose whether your child will get information and
promotional offers for things like music, video, and games.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.